(Early Merry Christmas)
(Christmas is nearing for the Rainbow Club too.)
Nice to see you all.
(Nice to see you.)
It's the warm and cozy time at the end of the year.
For the year-end vibe,
we prepared the best cakes of the cakes, the ice cream cakes.
- They're ice cream cakes. - You didn't know they were, right?
They look so beautiful.
Wrap up the year on a good note. It's the cozy time of the year.
- Let's blow out... - Okay.
The candles together.
One, two, three.
(Blowing out the candles)
Happy New Year.
This is creme brulee.
It's fun to crack the cake. See?
This is fun.
Like this.
(Taking a bite)
(A sweet flavor spreads in his mouth.)
You must have the ice cream with the creme brulee.
This one is good.
It's good.
- Let's try this too. - There are two different flavors.
(Taking a bite)
Kian84 is indeed on a different level.
(Fascinated)
(Let us take a bite of it too.)
This reminds me of hot chocolate.
- It's basically hot chocolate. - It tastes like hot chocolate.
Gosh, you have ice cream all over your chin.
Really?
- I guess you really like it. - It's good.
My gosh. Come on.
- This was a nice energy boost. - Yes.
Let's jump right into today's episode.
The member we'll meet this week...
has enough passion that can turn the coldest winter...
- into the hottest summer. - Yes.
He's the icon of fiery charisma.
Let's watch the clip to find out!
(Bring It On, Ghost)
- "Bring It On, Ghost?" - "Bring It On, Ghost?"
- Gosh, it's cold. - He's wearing workout clothes.
He's always wearing workout clothes.
They look different from his usual workout clothes.
- Really? - Yes.
(Current time: 7am)
People leave that early in the morning for marathons.
Gosh, what's taking them so long?
(He keeps pacing back and forth as it's cold.)
Is he waiting for someone?
(It's freezing.)
It was freezing that day.
It was a cold day. The temperature was minus 5°C.
(Shaking)
We have a long way to go.
(He keeps waiting for someone.)
- Come on, guys. - "Guys?"
(Lightening up)
Someone's here.
Come on, guys.
(A car pulls up in front of MINHO.)
Do you know what time it is?
It's been a while.
- Victory. - Victory.
At ease.
- It's been a while. - Who are they?
He saluted and said, "victory." Isn't it obvious?
- The Marines? - Let's go.
Victory.
I'm Choi Min Ho from the 1,245th intake.
"Victory."
(Once a Marine, forever a Marine.)
He looks sharp.
- The uniform suits him. - He's so cool.
Just looking at his face, I bet he was great in the Marines.
- Gosh, of course. - Of course.
I was in the 839th intake with the conscripted police.
What about you, Hyun Moo?
- You were in the KATUSA program. - I was in the KATUSA program.
- I was with the 39th... - Do you know your number?
(With the 39th...)
- What was that? - With the 39th intake?
No, I was just joking.
- There weren't any numbers, right? - I don't know mine.
- And let's be honest. - Does the army have that too?
I bet you can't remember those days anymore.
(It's hard to remember his days from the 20th century.)
- I mean, even I... - It feels like my previous life.
- Where did you serve? - I was with the Korea Coast Guard.
- Korea Coast Guard? - From Mokpo?
- We all served in different places. - Right.
- Conscripted police, Coast Guard, - Yes.
- I was with the Marine Corps. - Marine Corps,
- Army. KATUSA. - army, and KATUSA.
This rarely happens.
- You didn't serve? - Should I join the National Guard?
(Me?)
"You didn't serve?"
Gosh, this is awkward.
- She graduated from SNU. - Right, Seoul National University.
- SNU. - That's the most prestigious one.
- The most prestigious one. - She supervises people like us.
- That's right. - Right.
- She's the mastermind. - Yes.
- The car... - Gosh, it's so cold.
What took you so long?
- What's this? - We tried to get here fast.
- They're my dear comrades. - Have you been well?
Why didn't you bundle up more?
Hey, I thought my ears were going to fall off.
The three of us made good memories over the years.
They're younger than me, were above me in rank.
I started my day with them.
- I enlisted rather late. - You enlisted late.
We went through tough times together.
So we've bonded more.
Once we finished our service, we became good friends.
("MINHO Joins Final Training Instead of Taking His Day Off")
Why didn't you take your day off?
Why did you do that?
Around the time of my discharge,
a major field-training exercise was scheduled.
It was called Homeland Defense Training.
I really wanted to take part in that.
You know what? Even when you're determined...
- not to participate, - That's impressive.
- once you see your juniors... - Seriously. That's amazing.
(Once you see your juniors, you can't just walk away.)
- That's how I felt. - Right.
I thought, "Yes. I should..."
- "make one last good memory." - Right.
He'd only work out on his days off anyway.
- It didn't matter where he was. - He'd be doing the same thing.
- You're spot on. - But...
Even after we got discharged,
we naturally kept in touch and spent time together.
So we also went on a trip together.
I bet you guys are really close.
It's impossible not to bond.
About 20 to 30 people still gather when we hang out together...
- from time to time. - Really?
They were above me in rank.
But we're still good friends once we got out.
- My gosh. - Here we go.
Let's go.
Seeing you guys is bringing back old memories.
It's been a while since we're going on a trip.
I didn't even get to sleep for an hour today.
We were going on a trip together.
I was excited,
- so it was hard to fall asleep. - I bet.
- I fell asleep... - The World Cup Draw.
While watching the World Cup Draw.
Gosh, Korea is in a nice group.
I miss the executive officer.
- We should go and see him. - Is he in Pohang now?
He's in Pohang.
He's at the Airborne Training Center.
It's been five years since your discharge.
- You still keep in touch with them? - Yes.
I went to his house once a long time ago.
His wife gave us this half-dried saury salad.
- Gosh. - It was so good.
He sends us half-dried saury when it's in season.
Seriously.
Didn't we visit him last year?
We saw him...
- more than once every year. - Right.
We went to Gangwon Province...
- and Incheon. - Right.
You guys do meet often.
(Glancing)
You're used to driving the kids around.
You're a smooth driver.
- He's a father? - No.
- He's a taekwondo instructor. Yes. - He is?
Gosh, he's a taekwondo instructor.
When I worked as an art teacher, I used to drive the academy bus too.
- Really? - Really?
The director asked me if I could drive the bus...
on top of teaching them.
(Nudging him to take an extra rask)
I was like, "Hey, get in now."
- You had multiple tasks. - Multiple tasks.
The job was killing me.
Are you hogging up all the attention from the mothers?
I'm you at the taekwondo center.
(I'm you at the taekwondo center.)
He's easy-going.
You're still working there. You didn't quit.
- Did you get a girlfriend? - No.
How long has it been then?
No, MINHO. I had one before.
Stop lying.
- Because I never met her... - You think I'm always lying, right?
- Come on. Because I never met... - Why do you think he's lying?
- I know... - No, I had a girlfriend.
All about their dating history.
Have you still not gotten over your first love?
Gosh, no. Besides, she's not my first love.
It feels like only yesterday he was telling me about his love troubles.
She's getting married soon.
- Really? - Yes.
Wait. Who? Your first love?
- She's not my first love. - She's not.
From what I remember, a lot of people told MINHO...
about their love troubles.
People who were above me in rank came to me and asked my opinion...
about their future plans once they got discharged.
- They asked me for my advice. - Right. A lot of people did.
You're older than us, after all.
Asking the older guys is natural when you're in the military.
They came to me when they had exactly a month left.
And they told me about their life plans.
- Really? - Right.
- I was Dr. Oh Eun Yeong in there. - I bet.
Seriously.
- Our station had a good vibe. - We had a great vibe.
(They keep sharing stories about their military service.)
I bet it's fun.
When I meet my co-stars from plays again,
we always talk about the same thing.
- Right. - But we really like doing that.
- Right. That's what we need. - A bit of trouble makes it fun.
Daegwallyeong.
They drove to Gangwon Province.
I knew it. Spending time with fellow Marines...
makes one and a half hours fly by so fast.
I think we're almost there.
This is the place.
- Okay. Let's go. - We're here. Yes.
Gangwon Province.
Where is this place? A service area?
If it weren't windy today...
(Did the Marine trio get out at the service area?)
There he is.
(Laughing out loud)
- They're meeting up with someone. - They're meeting with more people.
- Lee Gi Mo. - Victory.
Victory.
(A man gives a disciplined salute.)
- How cute. - He looks cute.
I'm his favorite Marine.
I finally met my fellow Marine who was right below me in rank.
(Marine Lee Gi Mo, a direct junior of MINHO)
How old is he?
- He was born in 1998. - What?
He must've worked really hard in the military.
You might not know just by looking at him,
- but he has two kids. - My gosh.
- I see. - He's the most mature one then.
- Yes, in a way, he's our senior. - He's everyone's senior.
Right.
- He turned 27 this year, right? - Yes.
(MINHO, Gi Mo)
(He's the only junior of MINHO in today's group.)
The two seniors I met earlier...
enlisted before me.
So being with them was both comfortable and uncomfortable.
But as for Gi Mo,
he's my direct junior.
I can do whatever I want.
(Choi Min Ho: 1,245th intake, Lee Gi Mo: 1,246th intake)
Gi Mo and I served the longest together.
- He's your go-to guy. - Yes, he is.
He's your own Wilson.
I brought him everywhere.
Poor guy. He ended up with the wrong senior.
Gi Mo is from Gangwon Province.
He was born and raised there.
So when we were training in Pohang,
he always said that he'd take care of everything...
if we came to Gangwon Province.
Everyone says that.
So we actually went to Gangwon Province on a trip...
to catch up.
We had a blast on the trip too.
We decided to follow his lead and came to Gangwon Province again.
It's been a while.
(Not moving)
My gosh. He's not lowering his hand. This is so stressful.
The junior can't lower it until the senior does.
See? This isn't right.
Even his seniors aren't doing it.
At ease.
(As he was happy to see Gi Mo, the salute took a long time.)
Wait. Gi Mo has a big build.
- He's tall. - Yes, he's tall.
- Let's go inside. It's cold. - Let's go inside.
- Have you been well? - Yes, sir. Have you been well?
Your hair grew a bit.
- Really? - Yes.
He's still showing his respect to you as his senior.
- We do that to tease each other. - To tease each other?
We're in Gi Mo's hometown.
First of all,
we'll have some simple snacks at the top.
Can we buy ramyeon?
- Ramyeon sounds good. - Let's get ramyeon.
Today, I wanted us to get a taste of our old days...
or our old hardships, per se.
Our basic training was marching.
So we decided to hike.
- Why would you do that? - I see.
Gi Mo came up...
with this hiking trail on Seonjaryeong.
What do you want to eat?
- We can just pick the one we want. - Yes.
I'll go with this.
I like spicy ramyeon.
- I... - Gi Mo can't eat spicy food.
I'll go with beef-bone noodles.
(Finding him cute)
- Is this all? Do you want... - That's it.
- Really? This is it? - Yes.
- Are you sure? Okay. - Yes.
Let's go and pay.
I can tell that MINHO likes...
- I can see he likes Gi Mo. - Right.
- He takes good care of Gi Mo. - Gi Mo is his go-to guy.
- That's... - Have a good day.
- Can we get some hot water? - Sure.
You brought it.
- You're well-disciplined indeed. - Gosh. It's nothing.
I knew it, Shim Chang Eon. You're well-prepared.
To compliment someone, we say, "You're well-disciplined."
Hey, it might be really heavy.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors to decide who'll be carrying this.
- All done. - Okay.
Let's go.
Everyone wore their combat boots.
Of course.
They're wearing combat boots.
- They're wearing combat boots? - It looks like they're in training.
I also brought mine too.
We should all wear combat boots and hike.
Hey, look at that.
They're your combat boots...
- from five years ago? - Yes, they are my old combat boots.
Gosh, they look so cute.
- The military gives out good stuff. - They look cute.
Everyone, make sure to have your gear.
- Yes, sir. - Let's get changed.
- Get changed. - They brought their uniform too.
(I'm getting pumped up.)
- How is it? - I'm good.
This is good.
I can handle it.
Let's go.
It's so windy. They're not wearing a hat or gloves.
Hey, won't your ears get too cold?
We're the Marines.
So the Marines' ears don't get cold?
We overcome it with our passion.
If it gets too cold, we can remove one of our ears.
We're all pretentious a bit since we served in the Marines.
Right. But that's the fun of it. That's why you meet up.
- Is it this way? - I think it's this way.
You guys don't need to stretch before the hike, right?
- Of course. - We're good.
(Today's hiking trail begins...)
(from a small path next to the service area.)
"Pyeongchang County Mountain Climbing Guide Map."
There's the map.
Let's take a look before we go.
(Pyeongchang County Mountain Climbing Guide Map)
This is where we are. We're headed to...
- Seonjaryeong, right? - Yes.
I think Seonjaryeong is famous among backpackers.
- But... - Really?
The altitude is 1,157m?
The round trip is 11km? That's a piece of cake. Let's go.
- How is that a piece of cake? - Let's go.
The hiking trail reached an altitude of 1,100m.
The distance was about 11km.
An 11km hiking trail is considered really long.
It said it usually took around 4.5 hours.
But we were trained in military marching.
I thought we could shorten that time by an hour when we began.
(Highly motivated like a true Marine)
- Okay. Let's go. - Let's go.
But this isn't a trail running race.
I perceived it as my own training exercise.
- Sergeant Kim Tae Hwan. - Yes?
Shouldn't you guide us?
Why don't you show us how it's done? You're our senior.
- One, two, three, four. - Gosh.
Invincible Marines, shout it out. Go!
My gosh, you remember that.
- Of course. - Oh, my.
- Why did he say it like that? - The drill instructors...
don't want to lose their voice.
- They keep doing this. - Right.
- "Recruits!" - That's right.
- They do this to keep their voice. - Their voice would go hoarse.
That explains their vocalization.
- They need to control their voice. - I see.
"March." Like this.
Invincible Marines, shout it out. Go!
- I hate that sound. - I see.
That way, they won't lose their voice.
It's tough.
It's been a while since you all hiked, right?
- You too? - It's been a while for me too.
- Everyone, right? - Right.
Gi Mo, you said you came here two years ago.
- I came here just once. - I see.
- Gi Mo, no one gets left behind. - Yes, sir.
That's right, sir! No!
- He's only 27 years old? - He's 27.
- I get why you keep teasing him. - Right.
- He's adorable. - His reaction is fun to watch.
- I love his reaction. - Yes.
- That's why you hang out with them. - Right.
- You guys can't meet without him. - Gosh.
Gi Mo has to join us.
- There's always a guy like him. - Right.
For our crew, it was Kim Seok Gu.
I was the youngest for a long time when I served in the military.
- Really? - I bet his seniors loved him.
- Totally. - Yes, I agree.
Did you have fun in the military?
- I don't think he did. - There are so many things...
- I can't share on TV. - Right.
You know what? Listen.
- He can't share them on TV. - Hey, Ji Hyeon.
This is how I feel honestly when we talk about...
- our military service. - Okay.
You're not sharing your story. So I know how it must've been.
- We can't share our story. - No.
(I know everything.)
Those jerks.
I think our hiking trail is starting.
I doubt Gi Mo works out regularly.
I do.
- You mean soccer? - Yes.
Your yellow outfit makes you look like the leader.
Right.
It's already quite elevated.
- This was a beautiful trail. - It's beautiful.
How nice.
The vibe is changing here.
Didn't our training spot look similar to this?
- Hey, it looked just like this. - It's starting to look legit now.
This trail really looked similar to our training trail.
Doesn't it feel like we're really training?
Because I was based in Pohang,
I barely got to see snow while I served.
With the snow, it definitely felt different.
(They're no longer carrying the heavy military gear.)
(But like the day they met for the first time, )
(they hike in their combat boots during winter.)
Our combat boots are the best.
- Seriously. - Yes.
They look so cute hiking together.
They all must be in shape since they used to be Marines.
It just shows that all of us are tenacious by nature.
Chang Eon. Give me the bag. I'll carry it now.
I see. You guys are taking turns to carry the heavy backpack.
We decided to take turns.
But our seniors set an example.
The one in the highest rank...
- decided to carry it 1st. - He went 1st.
The one in the second-highest rank decided to go next.
It must have weighed at least 10kg.
It went over 10kg.
To be honest, it was fairly heavy. I was quite surprised.
- Let me know when it gets heavy. - Yes?
- I'm good. - My gosh.
- Gosh, the wind. - It's getting windier.
What time was it?
It was around 10:30am or 11am.
What's this?
Hey, look at this place.
- This might be a scenic spot. - My gosh.
- Oh, my. - Is that Gangneung?
My goodness.
(They arrive at the observatory in 30 minutes without breaks.)
It looked like CGI.
That was the ocean.
(Over the clouds and mountains, they see...)
My gosh. I can see the East Sea.
(the East Sea with blue waves.)
- This place looks beautiful. - How beautiful.
Look at the clouds moving. It's like a mirage.
(The clouds look unrealistic like CGI.)
The clouds look beautiful.
The sky looked beautiful too.
This place is crazy.
(It's so beautiful.)
This is nice. We ought to remember this view.
This place looks amazing.
I agree.
The view here is amazing...
at the top here.
The altitude is quite high.
Okay.
We still have a bit more to go. I think we have 2.5km to go.
Let's finish it.
That looks like the perfect spot to stop.
Gosh, we were just getting started.
We were only at a halfway point.
(The invincible Marines keep hiking without a sip of water.)
I'm hungry.
I'm starting to get hungry.
(The invincible Marine won't allow them to be weak even for a moment.)
You look so fresh even after an hour of hiking.
(With MINHO looking perfectly fine at the front, )
(the other Marines don't seem tired.)
(Panting)
(Breathing heavily)
(Marine Lee Gi Mo is getting out of breath.)
(Oh, no)
- I didn't know it was a dialect. - Me neither. I didn't know.
- Are you tired, Gi Mo? - No, sir.
- Everything's good. - Yes, sir!
(My dear Gi Mo)
You're not picking on each other for getting tired.
Gosh, it's crazy windy today!
- It's so windy. - It was crazy that day.
- Give it to me now. - I'm good.
Give it to me.
- Give me your bag then. - I'm good.
- Let's go. - You'll put it on top of yours?
Hey, this must've been heavy.
(He takes the backpack for them to share the burden.)
Tae Hwan, this is heavy.
My gosh. My body feels light now.
The determination to complete the task without giving up.
That's the spirit of Marines.
Hold on. The lady's backpack seems heavier.
- Forget about these Marines. - Right.
She's even carrying her dog.
Hey. You know?
- This is... - She's more hardcore...
- than you. - Hey.
You Marines need to stop bragging. You can't even beat moms.
- They carry so many bags of food... - Right.
- while talking on the phone. - The timing was crazy.
Look how comfortable the dog looks.
- It means she's steady as a rock. - That's right.
I bet the dog can even fall asleep since it's so comfy.
- Hey, this is crazy. - You guys are losing your touch.
It's the photo of the year.
Mothers beat the spirit of Marines.
Right.
- Hey, is that the place? - Yes, that's the peak.
(They only have 0.4km left until the peak.)
Gi Mo, how about a run?
I'll run.
Okay.
Run! Go!
- One, two. - Let's go.
- Left foot. - "Left foot."
Left foot.
I wonder why whenever four men get together,
they always end up doing stupid stuff like that.
- One, two, three, four. One, two. - One, two.
- One, two. - One, two.
- One, two. Let's beat this. - One, two.
- One, two, three, four. One, two. - Stop it.
(As MINHO tenaciously keeps on counting, )
(his comrades try to keep up.)
- They can keep up with you. - One, two.
Invincible Marines, shout it out. Go!
- Invincible. - Invincible.
- Marines. - Marines.
- Invincible Marines. - Invincible Marines.
- Marines, always victorious. - Marines, always victorious.
- Ghost-catching Marines! - Ghost-catching Marines!
- Gosh, we're almost there. - Let's go.
(Amazed)
We're almost there.
(They're so close to the peak.)
(They finish half of the trail in 1 hour and 20 minutes.)
You got there in 1 hour and 20 minutes.
Isn't that really fast?
Right. They're not on flat surface.
This place is huge.
(Out of breath)
(Oh, no. Poor Gi Mo.)
That was a crazy workout.
(We came, saw, and beat it.)
Gosh, that was a nice way to end it.
- You must be tired. - Good work.
(Baekdudaegan Seonjaryeong)
(Taking a picture to remember the moment)
We came all the way here to see this.
I felt proud.
We ran up toward the end.
Racing to the peak was the right call.
It made the trail even more rewarding.
It was quite windy,
but we didn't have to carry firearms.
We weren't wearing bullet-proof helmets either.
I felt so light without my gear.
This was a piece of cake for us.
I mean it.
One, two.
(They all take a selfie together.)
Okay.
That was neat.
(We did a neat job like true invincible Marines.)
Gosh, it's cold.
This place has a nice vibe.
Let's eat it on the ground. We can just elevate it.
Gosh, it must've been so cold...
- up there. - Yes.
Eating ramyeon at the top is different, though.
(Chuckling)
- Set it up. - I'll set it up.
- Gosh, I'm starving. - It looks so good.
(Everyone busily shakes their seasoning packet.)
We carry this heavy backpack for this, right?
That's right.
- I can't see. - A little bit more. Great.
(Pouring the steaming hot water)
It's warm.
I'm good.
Stop.
(Filling up their bowl in order)
- Everyone got their favorite. - That's good.
We got our favorite.
(Rummaging through)
Did you pack more food?
You can't have ramyeon without gimbap.
- What? - Gimbap.
Gimbap.
(Surprised)
I didn't know. But we had gimbap in the backpack.
- That's why it was heavy. - I bet the gimbap was heavy.
When did you pack this?
I got it this morning.
- You're well-disciplined. - Thank you, sir!
"Thank you, sir!"
I bought cheese and tuna gimbap.
- Gosh. - Okay.
(The table is filled with ramyeon and gimbap.)
They look good.
- Gosh, that does look good. - Right.
Should I have the gimbap first?
I bet it's good.
Gimbap is tasty when you eat it outdoors.
I want the tuna gimbap.
It's so good.
- I'm just sitting on the ground. - Gosh, that looks good.
- That looks so good. - My gosh.
Eat when the noodles are firm.
(Quickly slurping the noodles when they're still firm)
My gosh.
(This is what I'm talking about.)
This is a universal truth about ramyeon.
Ramyeon after a long day tastes the best.
I agree.
It was so good.
- It was really good. - Seriously.
(The unforgettable flavor...)
(after a hard day of training)
- Oddly, it tastes good outdoors. - Right.
- Right? - It's odd.
- It's better on a cold day too. - Right.
You need to sweat a bit after a good workout.
- Right. - It makes ramyeon tastier.
(The Marines gobble up the ramyeon.)
They must've been quite tired.
They must be happiest at that moment.
- Gi Mo, you know DELD, right? - Yes.
- DELD. - DELD.
DELD? Is it drink every last drop?
You must drink every last drop.
(Slurping the noodles first)
(Gulping it down)
(Hitting the spot)
(He drinks every last drop of it in an instant.)
(Feeling proud)
Let's clean this up.
(They clean up the spot where they ate.)
You know what? We came all the way here.
- We should take a picture. - Yes.
- Did you get it ready? - I'll get it ready.
We'll go shirtless if we don't have it.
(Go shirtless?)
(He takes off his jacket to take a picture.)
(What's going on?)
(A knowing smile)
I'll get it ready.
We'll go shirtless if we don't have it.
- Let's take one and go. - Get ready.
I haven't worn this in a while. It's been five years.
(Marine Corp)
(Sighing)
(They transform into true Marines.)
Seriously.
That was my idea.
Really?
It might offend some people when I say this.
All the military uniforms have the same digital camouflage pattern.
But the Marine uniform looks the best. I'm serious.
(But the Marine uniform looks the best. I'm serious.)
- My gosh. - Sure. I can see that.
- I'm serious. - I agree.
- I'm serious. - Sure.
Our uniform looks so much better.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
But we don't consider uniforms with that pattern authentic.
- What? - That's not a real uniform.
(The old-school ones are real.)
Hey. We didn't think highly of the Army uniform.
The Army uniform didn't look sharp.
The combat uniform conscripted police wear...
- Hey, don't be ridiculous. - looks really sharp.
Come on.
You just crossed the line. I'm serious.
- I swear. Our uniform is the best. - Hey.
Hey, that's not a real uniform.
We used to wear combat uniforms.
- I mean, field uniforms. - I see. Field uniforms.
They look great when worn properly.
But the Army uniforms don't look that cool.
The US military has the best uniforms.
(Do you know KATUSA?)
What are you talking about?
- Anyway, the old-school... - Haven't you seen the movie?
- The old-school one... - Haven't you seen it?
Looked weird and tacky.
Haven't you watched the move, "Saving Private Ryan?"
- Stand in front of that. - In front of that?
(The group dresses in red to take a picture.)
- All good? - Look over there.
Gi Mo's shirt got too small for him.
I thought he was Wilson.
- Red Wilson. - Wilson with a shirt on.
He's Red Wilson.
- Gosh, it's cold. - He's just so adorable.
Should I take off this jacket?
- Keep it on. That's better. - Keep it on.
- That's better than the sweater. - Okay.
(He wears the padded jacket instead of going shirtless.)
Ten, nine, eight, seven...
- Four, three, two. - Okay.
(Looking disciplined right away)
(We're the Marines.)
The uniform makes everyone behave the same way.
Okay.
Turn around.
(Turn around!)
We look like sausages.
- Six, five, - What kind of pose should we do?
- four... - Should we do this?
(Cringing)
(A ghost wouldn't even dare to come close at this vibe.)
We probably got it, right? Gosh, it's cold.
Okay.
(Grabbing)
(Look at this.)
(They conquer mountains after the sea.)
- Gosh, that's funny. - Okay.
That's a nice picture.
(They pack up after making a special memory.)
Let's go down with good energy.
Let's go.
Baekdudaegan Seonjaryeong, bye.
Bye.
Going down is easy.
(Baekdudaegan)
I like that song.
"I Choose to Become a Marine."
- But that's not a military song. - Right.
(Because I want to be a man)
(Singing it right away)
That's a real song?
It's one of the morning songs in the Marine Corp.
- You guys have a lot of songs. - We do.
On top of that, 1 of our top 10 military songs...
was written by our senior, Lee Chan Hyuk.
- He wrote a song too. - Yes. It's one of them.
The one from AKMU.
- The top ten military songs... - He wrote a military song?
He did. He wrote one for the Marines.
Conscripted police have songs too.
- But... - Do you remember any?
We have songs too.
(Trailing off)
(Stop the protesters)
(Face the stones)
(We can take sick leave then)
Forget about this awful military service
(Dancing)
There can't be military songs like that.
I don't think that's the official song.
- I see. He changed the lyrics? - Military songs...
- get new lyrics among soldiers. - Right.
I was stationed to stop the protesters.
- So I saw a lot of protesters. - Right.
We changed the lyrics of the songs the protesters sing.
- It goes back and forth. - Yes.
- What about the Coast Guard? - The Coast Guard...
(Stop the illegal crab boats)
No.
(Military songs with illegally changed lyrics are everywhere.)
(They come down quickly as they think about military songs.)
That was a quick hike.
Yes.
How long did it take?
- We were quick. - It took us three hours.
- Three hours. - We were really quick.
Gosh, we came back down fast.
- Three hours? - Yes.
Now that we finished our hike,
let's go and have some fun.
Sounds good.
- Gi Mo, sit in the back. - Yes, sir.
(The hike usually takes 4 hours and 30 minutes.)
(They finish the hike within 3 hours and 20 minutes.)
(Looking full of energy)
Gi Mo's face looks pale.
Gi Mo's dark circles got bigger.
Let's go.
- Here we go. Let's go. - I wonder where they'll go next.
(I love you)
(Now that he's done with the hike, he seems cheerful.)
(Laughing)
- They're singing back and forth. - Seriously, Gi Mo.
He's good at lightening the mood.
Gosh, he's a top instructor.
(They keep on driving without taking any breaks.)
I think we're here.
- What? - What?
- A ski resort? - Okay. Let's go.
(A white snowy path stretches out on the mountain.)
(Another winter sport)
(They arrive at the winter training center after hiking.)
- Really? - Gosh, it's a ski resort.
Let's go.
It's longer than it looks.
- Yes, it is. - It's been a while for me.
There are a lot of ski resorts in Gangwon Province.
But all of us aren't good at skiing.
So we decided to do a simple, but fun activity.
With this, we can go back to our childhood.
- We went snow sledding instead. - Yes.
(The slope seems too low for Marines.)
I bet Gi Mo will go down fast.
- Seriously. - Weight affects the speed.
This is the second activity planned by Marine Lee Gi Mo.
With this, we can be children again.
It's snow sledding, full of good old memories.
He picked a great activity.
I think it had been 20 years since I'd last gone snow sledding.
- It had been so long. - It's faster than you think.
I've never gone sledding in my life.
- Snow sledding? - Yes.
Really?
- Because it's too warm in Mokpo? - It doesn't snow there?
You've never tried it with the rice sack around your home?
- Right. - I've done that.
- You have? - Right. I've done it with the sack.
But I've never been to a real sledding hill.
- I see. Not the sledding hill. - I've never been to a ski resort.
Me neither.
- Really? - Why not?
- I've never gone skiing. - Were you busy studying?
I didn't like the cold.
I bet you stayed in a warm library.
That's right.
(A library kept her warm in the middle of winter.)
- She rode the books, not sleds. - Of course.
She was busy reading, so she had no time for sledding.
I'm really excited right now.
It has been so long.
What will we do if they can't hold us?
I don't think they'll be able to hold Gi Mo.
I'll do my best to hold out.
I'll stop on my own.
(Excited)
(I'm excited as well.)
That's how you come down.
- It spins. - The sled spins.
It's fast.
It looks fun.
- I love ski slopes. - It's fast.
(They arrive at the starting point with excitement in their hearts.)
"First-time riders' entrance and tube pickup area."
It's this way.
Do we line up here?
Since it's your first time,
- you don't need to line up. - Okay.
- You can line up next time onward. - Okay.
When you're a first-time rider, there's a safety issue.
- It can be a bit dangerous. - Okay.
So they let you go one at a time.
That way, you learn how to ride safely.
- The 1st-time riders? - The 1st-time riders...
- don't go down together. - It's to prevent a crash.
- It's to prevent a crash. - That's right.
All right.
(Gi Mo gets ready to ride it first.)
It's this one.
- You know... - Gi Mo is heavy.
When you see the blue net,
- put your feet down to stop. - Okay.
Before that...
It's really fast. It's faster than you think.
It looks fun.
- Gi Mo, go first and wait for us. - Okay.
(He's all ready.)
Okay.
Gi Mo is going down.
- It's like parachute training. - It's like parachute training.
It's nerve-racking.
(Meanwhile, Marine Gi Mo awaits...)
(parachute training in a nervous state.)
We had parachute training...
- with the paratroopers. - Did you do that as well?
- Yes. - My goodness.
All of them have jumped from an aircraft.
That's impressive.
- Did Gi Mo jump as well? - Gi Mo jumped as well.
Do you feel like Gi Mo didn't jump?
Gi Mo did all the training.
I bet Gi Mo was the strongest Marine in the military.
- He was a dependable Marine. - Of course.
(Even though sledding is easier than parachuting, )
He's holding on tight.
(he's nervous.)
There he goes.
(Shouting)
(He sets off with a scream.)
He has jumped from an aircraft.
(Here comes Mr. Octagonal Cap!)
(He goes down fast.)
- It's fast. - It's really fast.
It accelerates a lot.
Gi Mo is going well.
- He's really fast. - My goodness.
It's very long.
- It's very long. - Why is it so long?
They won't be able to catch him because he's heavy.
My goodness.
All right.
(The Marines take the sled down.)
Children ride with the adults.
That's right. It's dangerous.
- They ride like that. - Children aren't scared of that.
- Children can't speed up. - That's right.
(They're more excited than children.)
(Men in an octagonal hat)
It snowed when we were sledding.
It was so romantic.
It began to snow when we arrived at the ski resort.
- I see why Gi Mo wore the hoodie. - It was so much fun.
- It's romantic. - It was romantic.
Let's have a bet for coffee.
- A bet for coffee? - A bet for hot coffee.
- All right. - We knew who'd place first,
so we decided to make the last place pay.
The three of us were similar.
- In terms of weight? - Yes.
- Let's go. - Why am I nervous?
- What will be the finish line? - What will be the finish line?
- The finish line. - The end of the blue line.
- The end of the blue line? - Yes.
It's a matter of who passes the end of the blue line first.
Gi Mo has so much advantage...
- because of his weight. - I'll place first.
- It's your turn. - Okay.
(The Marines enter the battlefield.)
- Let's go. - Drum roll.
(The mission involves protecting the wallet...)
(and drinking free coffee!)
- Tae Hwan is at a disadvantage. - Okay.
- He's at a disadvantage. - Okay.
Don't even think of a false start.
Of course not.
(Which Marine will place last?)
Last place will buy coffee.
- Okay. - Last place will buy coffee.
- Just avoid placing last. - Let's go.
- Marines, are you ready? - Yes!
Let's go.
- Are they doing a slogan for this? - Let's go.
That's the fun of it.
Let's go.
(They set off!)
- Let's go. - Gi Mo doesn't disappoint.
Gi Mo is fast.
He's unrivaled.
No one can beat him.
(Marine Gi Mo takes the lead.)
- Let's go. - It's fast.
It's fast.
(A fierce competition to get ahead)
Gi Mo is too fast.
What?
(This is fun.)
(He gets covered in snow.)
(Marine Gi Mo remains at the front.)
He's catching up.
(A match for the pride of the Marines)
Let's go.
Who will win?
You and I are tied.
(1st place, Marine Gi Mo)
I came in last.
- Who is it? Me? - It's me.
- Is it you, Chang Eon? - Yes.
Gi Mo is so fast.
It was fun.
Well done.
Hot caffe latte...
- and hot caffe Americano. - It has the ski resort vibe.
It's romantic.
As we get snowed on...
Let's drink coffee as we get snowed on.
This is incredible.
(They avoid the eaves to get snowed on.)
- You wanted to get snowed on. - Yes. We stood there on purpose...
to get snowed on.
(This is romance.)
It's really hot.
I bet you felt really good when it snowed.
I felt really happy. It was so romantic.
Gi Mo, where are we going next?
We're going to our hometown,
- Jumunjjin. - Jumunjjin?
- Let's go. - Jumunjjin.
Did you reserve a nice restaurant?
- A nice restaurant? - I'm so hungry.
There's no problem with the menu.
- He's a local. - Let's go.
Will there be hot soup?
There'll be hot soup.
(Excited)
Today is Gi Mo's training day.
We're in Gangwon Province, so we need to check.
- We filled up the romantic vibes. - We filled up the romantic vibes.
Chang Eon, are you okay with driving?
Of course. This is my job.
- MINHO. - Yes?
Let's decide on the menu.
There'll be scallops and pen shells.
Shall we order sashimi as well?
Let's eat what you want to eat.
- Let's eat sashimi as well. - Yellowtail.
Assorted sashimi.
(He takes out his phone right away!)
Bro, can we order some sashimi as well?
- It's run by his friend. - What kind of sashimi is there?
(He's good.)
Flatfish?
Please prepare that.
- Okay. - He makes sure...
to give everyone a treat.
It's so convenient when you have a friend who is a local.
The jang kalguksu we ate back then...
- was so tasty. - Seriously.
We ate it with young radish kimchi.
That was soon after So Mi's birth.
So Mi came as well.
Yes, So Mi came as well.
Thank goodness your daughter resembles your wife.
She resembles me too.
I was cute when I was little.
"I was cute when I was little."
When did your looks change drastically?
My looks changed when I braved the strong winds of Jumunjin.
It was the storm.
He's witty.
- He's charming. - He's charming.
- It's really windy. - The winds are strong.
It's that way.
Those restaurants are bound to be tasty.
Let's go.
(Let's go and eat.)
- Is it this place, Gi Mo? - Yes.
(Excited)
Let's go.
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
(My goodness)
Hey, the view is cool.
Gosh, Gi Mo.
Everything is in order.
(You can see it right away when you enter.)
- Oh, my gosh. - My goodness.
The view was insane. I was so surprised.
(Even the view is romantic!)
Nice.
Hey, Gi Mo.
- The view is in order. - This is incredible.
It's so nice.
- It's so nice. - This place is incredible.
Gi Mo is good.
I picked a nice place.
(Proud)
Look at how proud he is.
(Laughing)
- He did it. - He did it.
- You made up for the past mistake. - Jumunjin.
He's different on his home ground.
Hello.
- Let's put them on the grill. - The flame is coming up.
- It's the briquette fire. - The briquette fire is nice.
(The main dish, grilled shellfish appears.)
Okay.
- This is incredible. - It's here.
Let's take a photo.
(The side dishes that'll warm up the stomachs)
This is insane.
The side dishes look good.
(Next to them...)
(is a tray that's full of fresh shellfish.)
- Shellfish. - They look delicious.
You must eat grilled shellfish at a place like that.
(A shellfish meal that captures the sea)
- Let's eat a fishcake each. - Let's eat a fishcake each.
(They each take a fishcake.)
(He takes a big bite.)
(Impressed)
It looks tasty.
- I'm hungry after playing. - Yes.
Let's grill some shellfish with cheese.
- This one? - Yes.
(They listen to Gi Mo and grill the scallops with cheese.)
Let's grill four.
- Scallops. - Scallops are the tastiest.
(Yes.)
They look tasty.
(Their mouths water.)
- Okay. Let's eat. - Let's eat.
Enjoy the food.
- This is incredible. - There's a way to eat.
- Is there a way to eat? - Eat it with meat...
so that it feels like samhap.
- That's right. Samhap. - With meat?
Put pork belly on the top...
- and add a bit of chojang. - Pork belly.
- Then chojang? - Yes, chojang.
Chojang.
- Do we eat them together? - Yes. Pick them up.
Like samhap.
(Taking a big bite)
(Humming in approval)
(The shellfish samhap is insane.)
(They give a thumbs up without a word.)
(Everyone makes and eats samhap.)
It's different when you eat...
- by the sea, right? - Of course.
- The location plays a big role. - It's really tasty.
(The food tastes better since they're by the sea.)
It's so tasty.
(Approaching)
(Sashimi and assorted seafood get served next.)
The table will break.
This is incredible.
This is the real deal.
It's to die for.
- Look at the oyster. - You can eat it as it is.
- You can eat it raw. - Look at the size.
How is it so big?
(Raw scallops...)
(and raw abalones)
This is the real deal.
Everything looks fresh.
Seriously, everything was fresh.
There must be a reason why there's the salt and sesame oil sauce.
(He dips it in the salt and sesame oil sauce.)
- My goodness. - It must be tasty.
Let's begin.
This is the sauce for sashimi.
Makjang?
Dip it in the salt and sesame oil sauce just once.
(He tackles the scallop sashimi!)
- It's incredible. - It's so tasty.
It's incredible.
It looks tasty.
(They even eat spicy fish soup.)
They need to wrap up with a spicy dish.
(My goodness)
Oh, my.
- It's so tasty. - It's so tasty.
We never fail when we follow Gi Mo.
(They're serious about every bite.)
We couldn't talk...
because we were so hungry.
We kept eating because the food was tasty.
- People only say, "It's tasty." - Yes.
(Staring)
It feels strange to see Gi Mo with long hair.
- To be honest, - Seaman recruit's hair?
It suits him the best.
Gi Mo looked the best with this hair.
- Let me see. - Oh, my.
- He looked strong. - Seriously.
My goodness.
He must've been younger than 27 back then.
He was in his early 20s. He was 21.
- What? - My goodness.
- He was 21. - He looked so strong.
Seriously.
(Giggling)
Seriously, you looked so scary.
- You'll get everyone in a war. - I'm more naive than you think.
One time, he cut his hair long for his leave.
- That's right. - He looked strange.
- "It doesn't suit you." - "It doesn't suit you."
(Short hair suits you the best.)
How about Ye Yeong?
- May I call her right now? - What?
- Ye Yeong? - Yes.
Where is she right now?
- His wife? - She's at home.
- That's right. - I see.
You're close enough to call her by her name.
Yes.
(He calls his wife.)
Victory.
For the first time in a while,
I came to Jumunjin with my senior Marines.
- Victory. - Victory.
Everything is in order.
What? How did you lose so much weight?
How did you lose so much weight?
I went on a diet.
You entered a competition.
- That's right. - Yes.
- I did that. - Well done.
(He even knows what she has been up to.)
Please take Gi Mo with you and help him exercise.
- His belly became so big. - Oh, no.
His belly became so big. It's a problem.
All right. Let's meet next time.
- Okay. - Bye.
Ye Yeong lost so much weight.
Bye.
I received it.
(How cute)
I had a very romantic day.
It was joyous and a bit childish.
I went back to the old days...
and regained my innocence.
It's a page in my youth...
that won't come back.
With this energy,
I'll be able to be brave every day...
and move forward.
To me, the Marine Corps is...
the road I chose...
that'll go on forever.
If anyone asks me to go back, I can go back...
- as a petty officer. - Go back.
As a petty officer.
(He stresses it.)
Let's go to Pohang next.
- That sounds good. - Gi Mo, let's go to Pohang next.
I'm always ready.
I'm happy.
(My Youth Will Last Forever)
We enjoyed the video.
They became your close friends.
- Yes. - I'm very jealous. It's so nice.
Would you like to go to the Marine Camp?
(What?)
Marine Camp?
Shall we go to the Marine Camp on I Live Alone?
I refuse to go since I served in the army.
I can't go since I was a conscripted policeman.
You can't go since you served in KATUSA, right?
I need permission from the US Army.
(They're ridiculous.)
(I Live Alone)
(Things to Be Thankful For)
(Dusting)
I feel like your house is becoming smaller.
It's because I took out my winter clothes.
- It became a bit smaller. - Your winter clothes.
I'll fold it.
(Let's see.)
It's 10:36am.
(He makes his bed as he checks the time in the morning.)
(Clean)
Let's eat first.
I'll make egg rice.
(He'll eat a simple meal of the soy sauce egg rice.)
(He pours oil into the hot pan.)
(Cracking)
(He cracks open an egg and drops it into the pan.)
There are two yolks.
- There are two yolks. - Two yolks.
- It feels good. - That's right. It feels good.
I'm off to a good start.
(I got lucky.)
(Cutting)
(He slices chili peppers on the kitchen counter.)
(Fascinated)
Let's make it spicy.
(He adds spiciness.)
(He pours a bit of soy sauce over the double-yolk egg.)
Why do you pour soy sauce directly over the egg?
That's my secret.
- Really? - The burnt soy sauce...
gives it a smoky flavor.
It's much tastier to add that to rice.
- It's for a smoky flavor. - Yes.
Good.
(The simple dish of soy sauce egg rice is complete.)
- That's how you eat it. - It looks tasty.
Let's make it spicy.
(Wiping)
He eats like Hyun Moo.
You eat standing up.
I've begun to do that. It feels good.
I guess I made it trendy.
You think the world revolves around you, Hyun Moo.
(Moo-centric theory is the truth!)
(He joins on the trend without even realizing it.)
It smells so tasty.
It's really tasty with chili pepper.
(Halting)
Did she leave her phone on the bus?
(He calls someone in the middle of mixing the rice.)
Did she leave it at home?
- My baby. - Mom.
What? I see.
- Hey. - At what time will you arrive?
It said that it'd take 2 hours and 20 minutes.
You got on the bus at 10am, right?
Yes. I set off at 10am.
Okay.
- I love you. - Okay.
Gosh, ma'am.
My mom hasn't come to my place in a long while.
So she decided...
to come to my place for the first time in a while...
and see if I was living well.
(It's the day his mom is visiting.)
To park my car at the bus terminal...
and pick my mom up,
I needed 40 to 50 minutes.
That meant I needed to leave the house by 11:30am.
To avoid her nagging... I mean, to avoid her advice,
I needed to clean the house.
So I didn't have time to eat at the table.
That was why I ate quickly while standing up.
That was why you ate while standing up.
- You didn't have time. - You need to work fast.
If you don't clean up, your mom does it.
Yes. Then my belongings disappear.
That isn't the issue. It's hard on your mom.
It's hard on my mom.
Whenever my mom visits, my belongings disappear.
- I know how you feel. - Of course.
Your mom cherished you and raised you well.
Do announcers tend to be unfilial?
- That's the criterion. - Is that the criterion?
Yes. The first criterion of being an announcer is...
- the lack of filial piety. - The lack of filial piety.
Is that a part of the test?
- Yes. It's a part of the interview. - Is there a score...
- for the lack of filial piety? - Yes.
(The Lack of Filial Piety)
(1. What do you do when you need to barp during a call with Mom?)
(Don't hold it in.)
(2. Whose duty is handwashing my clothes?)
(My mom's duty)
(He gets a high score when it comes to the lack of filial piety.)
Only the announcers understand.
It's the world of announcers.
(It's a virtue for us.)
(He'll be filial today since his mom is visiting.)
(Eating)
(Humming in approval)
(There's no relaxation...)
(he showed last time.)
(Eating hurriedly)
He's shoving in food since he needs to eat fast.
(Eating)
(He quickly finishes eating while standing up.)
(He quickly does the dishes.)
What time is it now?
It's 11am. I'm a bit behind.
I need to clean the house quickly.
(He needs to finish cleaning in 30 minutes.)
The veranda is in a terrible state.
There's a lot to clean up.
You don't have enough time.
I bet your mom will say, "Why is the veranda so messy?"
- My goodness. That won't do. - I'm sure of it.
"Do you live alone to be so messy?"
I think she'll say something.
(This won't do.)
What's that?
(He pulls a canopy over it.)
He pulled a canopy over it.
I hid it under the cloth.
It's okay. I can do it.
Let's put them inside.
It's like cleaning the barracks.
He seems like a soldier.
(He spins the container to keep it out of his mom's sight.)
You spun it to keep it out of her sight.
(Let's see.)
Let's put it here.
It'll hide the stove.
He's hiding everything.
All right.
(He displays cool items.)
I'll display it so that my mom can see it.
The autographed T-shirt.
I interviewed Heo Hoon.
I need to make her happy.
What time is it now?
(It's already 11:15am.)
Don't you need to get ready and head out?
(To avoid his mom's advice, )
All right.
(he needs to clean up as much as he can!)
Time passes quickly when you clean up.
That's right.
Let's change it.
(He works fast to hide the dirty parts of the house.)
What time is it now?
I need to head out.
Still...
- The things I'm thankful for. - What?
- Is he writing a diary? - He still does that.
- Why do that when he's so busy? - I know.
Firstly, I'm thankful...
that Mom can come to Seoul in a healthy state.
I'm thankful that the weather is cold.
Good.
(After completing his morning routine)
(Adjusting)
Mom likes it when I wear a tie.
A tie.
Not bad.
- She likes it when you look neat. - Yes.
- When you meet your parents, - Yes.
It's important to wear neat clothes.
It's a way of showing them that you're living well.
That makes sense.
When they see their son looking neat and pretty,
- they feel proud. - That's right.
I made a lot of effort since she doesn't visit often.
(He puts a lot of care into getting ready.)
All done.
(Spraying)
(He sprays air freshener.)
You're putting a lot of care into it.
The woody fragrance will smell natural.
Why are you spraying so much?
My mom is sensitive when it comes to smell.
- Really? - Yes.
(Spraying)
What? Aren't you spraying too much?
Is your mom visiting for inspection?
- Is she an inspector? - Will she wear white gloves...
and do this?
"Did you wipe this part?"
Let's go.
(Mom, I'm on my way.)
(At 11:40am, he finally sets off.)
The weather is nice.
(He heads over to the bus terminal as he listens to music.)
Mom likes Lee Eun Ha.
"You Let Me Go with a Smile."
(He finishes setting up the playlist.)
You're attentive.
I always play old songs.
- A playlist of her favorite songs. - Yes.
Old songs.
(He drives as he listens...)
(to his mom's favorite songs.)
(He sees his destination.)
(Glancing over)
It's 12:10pm. She'll be here in 15 minutes.
(As he checks the arrival time of the bus his mom is on, )
(he arrives at the bus terminal.)
(He fixes his clothes before meeting her.)
- Kang Yong, you look cool. - He looks cool.
It's 12:21pm. I'm late.
(Flustered)
(Feeling pressed for time, he quickens his steps.)
It's 12:21pm. She'll be here soon.
She'll be here in one minute.
(It's 1 minute before her arrival, so he speeds up even more.)
She must be here. I need to hurry up.
Where is she?
My goodness.
This is the gate.
(Chuckling)
I knew you'd do this.
She currently lives in Gunsan, North Jeolla Province.
She traveled a long way.
(In the fridge of Kang Yong who lives alone)
- I see. - She makes me sticky rice.
(I watched today's episode...)
(of "News Anhani," the Youtube channel.)
(She monitors his shows...)
(and gives him a thumbs up.)
You brought so many things.
Did she bring those boxes alone?
I tell her to bring just a little bit,
- but she doesn't listen. - Of course not.
Even when you tell her to bring just a little bit,
- she brings a lot. - Yes.
She loads the compartment.
- Just two. - Really?
They aren't very heavy. Take a hot pack.
It's okay.
Let's go.
Why did you bring so many things?
Did you have breakfast?
- Yes, I did. - I see.
I had egg rice.
- Egg rice? - Yes.
- Did you have breakfast? - I had breakfast as I always do.
I also had a snack on my way here.
- What did you eat? - What?
- What did you eat? - The way you talk...
"Did you have lunch?"
(Homely)
I make an effort to be affectionate.
How old is your mom?
She was born in 1960.
She had me at a late age.
- You were born late. - I was born late.
She had me at the age of 36 or 37.
I see.
That's why you care about her more.
Yes.
- I had this. - Okay.
Okay.
It's cold, so don't take it out.
Sit in the back. I'll do it, Mom. Just get in the car.
- Is the door open? - Yes.
I'll put them on the seat like this.
- Give me your bag. - Can I get in now?
- It's okay. I need to drink. - Really?
- I need to drink. - It's a heartwarming sight.
I'll close the door.
You look after your mom.
I see the resemblance.
- He looks the same. - He has her nose and mouth.
- That's right. - Yes.
Many people tell me that I take after my mom.
I recently read something.
Mom finds her children beautiful because they're like...
a time machine that takes her back to her most beautiful days.
(They're like a time machine.)
They have their mom's face.
It's a way to see herself...
- in her most beautiful days. - You're right.
Seeing them together reminds me of those words.
I see.
My mom gets angry...
when people say that I take after her.
- "Why..." - Your mom gets angry?
Yes. "Why do you say that he takes after me?"
- It depends on the mom. - Yes.
Turn on the heater, Mom.
Is your body okay? Doesn't it feel heavy?
My body is okay.
Let's go.
(They head home.)
Tomorrow is the first anniversary of you passing the announcer exam.
Tomorrow?
(Seoul is as welcomed as the news of her son passing the exam.)
I love this song so much.
I sing it very often.
Kang Yong is attentive.
(The playlist he put together for his mom is a success.)
- Mom, you need to get off first. - Okay.
Get off first.
(She listens to her son and gets off quickly.)
Let's go.
(Let's go.)
- Let's go. - All right.
The doors to the netherworld opened.
She's here for inspection.
- He'll get a bomb of advice. - Yes.
Let's go.
(Nervous)
It's fragrant, right?
- Can you smell it? - It smells nice.
- Yes, it smells nice. - My goodness.
You put eggs on top of the stove.
My goodness.
It began as soon as she arrived.
She started off lightly.
It smells nice, right?
(My goodness)
- It has been a while, so... - It smells nice.
- You distract her with fragrance. - Yes.
- It only smells nice. - "It only smells nice."
It smells nice since I've cleaned the house.
It smells nice since you've cleaned the house.
Mom, give me your coat. I'll hang it up.
- It's okay. Hold on. - I kept talking to her...
- in order to distract her. - You tried to distract her.
It's your first time seeing Wilson, right?
(He distracts her with Wilson this time.)
Wilson is here. I can't believe it.
- Hug it. - I can't believe it.
I saw it on TV all the time.
I wanted to hug it.
- He succeeded in distracting her. - Come here.
- It was a good strategy. - Yes.
Nice to meet you, Wilson.
I thought I'd only see it on TV.
I got to hug Wilson thanks to my son.
Mom, this is the jacket you bought me.
It's pretty.
It's neat, right?
- You wore it on purpose. - It's neat.
- That's right. - You keep talking to her...
- so that she can't look around. - I keep talking to her.
You don't give her time to nag at you.
- Nice. - Let's take a look.
Mom, take a seat.
The house is cleaner than you thought, right?
There's hair on the floor.
- It can't be like your place. - You got caught.
Do you have a lint roller?
I do, but I can vacuum the floor.
(Cutting)
Why have you brought so much?
- Gosh. - Gosh.
Oh, my gosh.
What is all this? Let's go over them one by one.
This is the yakbap.
- Yakbap? - Yes.
Here.
(Excited)
- They all got squished on the way. - Gosh!
How did she make that?
Ever since I was in elementary school,
my mother made yakbap in the exact same way.
- It must taste amazing. - It's great.
It looks like it was made at a rice cake shop.
- This is glutinous rice, right? - Yes.
It must taste good to have it now.
It will taste good now.
This is homemade kimchi.
This tastes great.
Gosh, that looks good.
(Grabbing)
(He puts it straight into his mouth.)
The kimchi tastes so good.
- Does it taste good? - Yes.
(Feeling proud)
No matter what kind of good kimchi I get from elsewhere,
it tastes different from my mom's kimchi.
There's a big difference.
Try some of the meat.
- Gosh, it's jangjorim! - Jangjorim!
- Here's some suyuk. - That's great.
I didn't bring that much.
- Kimchi? - This is raw skate.
Gosh, seasoned raw skate!
- This is the braised skate. - Your signature dish.
Two pieces of braised skate.
What's this? Buchimgae?
- No way. - Shrimp jeon.
It's like a holiday.
How many dishes have you brought?
(She even brought the soft persimmon that she peeled herself.)
She peeled the soft persimmon?
She scooped all of it into the bowl.
(Feeling grateful)
She's an excellent cook.
Gosh, are you serious?
The size of the dishes is perfect for someone living alone.
She packed them into reasonable portions.
Right.
That's perfect for someone living alone.
It's just enough with a bowl of rice.
- That's so considerate of her. - Right.
That's amazing.
Right.
But there's something else.
- The wall feels empty here. - Right.
- What did you bring? - I brought something to hang up.
Also,
- A photo? - place this at the entrance.
- Gosh! - It's a lucky broom.
A lucky broom?
- Here. - I thought it was a bottle of wine.
No. It's a lucky broom.
(Touching)
I think it was since this summer.
She started learning fabric art.
So she made that.
She takes classes twice a week.
It's literally drawing on fabric.
She usually draws plants.
But she has a great talent in drawing.
She has a great artistic touch.
Should I put it up here?
No. I think it'll look better here.
I think it can be put up here.
- There? Sure. - Yes.
The lucky broom represents sweeping in luck.
Very lightly.
There you go. That should be enough.
It has to be stuck right away.
Will it work?
- Yes. - Did it work?
It worked.
It looks nice.
It suits the house.
- No. - The smaller one should go here.
The bigger one there and the smaller one here.
(Reaching out)
(His mother's fabric art frames fill the wall.)
She brought her work.
Awesome.
- She drew them herself. - Really?
The one on the right looks really nice.
Instead of going with the same style,
I think she will do really well with whatever she wants to draw.
Don't you have some tea for me?
- Tea? - Yes.
She suddenly asked for some tea.
- Tea. - Do you want some tea?
Yes. Actually...
Did you bring something?
I brought the tea mats that I made as well.
It would be nice to have some tea with these.
She wanted to use those.
- She wanted to use those? - Right.
While having some coffee...
- Would you like some coffee? - Yes.
Do you not have any wet wipes?
- I do, Mom. - Where?
Right here.
(Pass me the wet wipes.)
Gosh.
She's going to start cleaning.
- It has begun. - She's cleaning that part?
It must've been here for a while. It won't come off.
It's the part under the table...
- when you carry it. - Right.
Right at that moment when he left the room.
(Walking on eggshells)
That's just a trace of me, Mom.
These unclean traces don't need to be left.
Gosh, it has begun.
The battle has begun.
(He starts feeling anxious.)
(Sighing)
I should've brought the drinks quickly.
Right.
This is what's fascinating about all mothers.
- They use wet wipes really well. - Right.
They use one sheet...
- for several hours. - Right.
It's a bit...
(She places the coasters nicely.)
Why did you place three?
- Is this for Wilson? - Yes.
The house is neat, isn't it?
It's neater than you thought,
- right? - Sure.
(Chuckling)
(I'll sit next to Mom.)
(She takes a sip of the warm tea her son made.)
(I'll take a sip as well.)
Let's clean up.
These should go in the trash.
I clean up right away, Mom.
The sink.
- I clean up right away. - I need to take a look.
"Give me some credit, Mom."
Look. I clean up like this right away.
"I've changed."
(Sighing)
(Looking around)
(His heart sinks at the sound of his mother's sigh.)
- "Look at this." - She shouldn't see the gas stove.
Hold on.
Honestly, can't I be allowed to clean this once?
- Gosh, she spotted it. - There.
- It doesn't need to be cleaned. - Bring me the rag I brought.
It won't come off.
Moms can make it come off.
(She makes a check for the closet under the sink.)
I tidied up this area last time.
- It's a mess again. - She's performing an inspection.
It has begun.
Gosh.
(Walking on eggshells)
I tell her not to do it,
but she cleans everything whenever she comes.
- My goodness. - She couldn't be stopped.
She can't stand it.
Hold on.
(He heads somewhere while walking on eggshells.)
(Kang Yong gets something out from the microwave.)
Mom, try the walnut cake.
- He's trying to distract her. - It's really good.
He's blocking her mouth.
(She lets him put it in her mouth.)
It's hot, right? It's good.
- Isn't it too hot for her? - Does it have red beans in it?
It's hot.
(It's hot.)
Look over here.
(Giving up)
- Gosh, it's hot. - He's really walking on eggshells.
Don't you become like that? I'm the same.
- Well, I just... - When my mom starts cleaning,
I feel anxious.
- Really? - Yes.
Hold on.
- Lift the coffee machine. - This?
Yes.
She might end up cleaning the whole house...
starting with that.
My goodness! This part is the worst!
Be careful.
Gosh, unbelievable.
This part...
- Gosh. - Forget it. I'll do it.
I washed this in the morning.
I'll wash them later.
(His mom starts washing the dishes.)
I'll do it.
- She hasn't even begun. - I'll do it.
I'll do it. It needs to be done with dish soap.
(The son's calls are useless to the mother.)
This will be put away.
(The dishes are washed in a flash.)
Done. Done, right?
- I need to check the bathroom. - The bathroom is fine.
The bathroom.
(Feeling anxious)
Gosh.
(I have to clean it all over.)
I felt bad about it.
- Of course. - I tried to stop her,
- but she wouldn't listen. - As it might be too exhausting?
Right.
Look at the toilet getting cleaned.
I tell her not to do it, but she won't listen.
Gosh.
She cleans things until she gets satisfied.
In the end,
I thought it was better to give her a massage...
while she worked.
My mom can't be stopped.
That's enough, Mom.
This is a method I figured out.
"Mom, don't do it!"
- This will never work. - Right.
That is why I prepare a gift for her instead.
- My mom draws as well. - Right.
When I suggest going to an art supply store...
that is nearby,
she stops cleaning right away.
- You go for her greatest interest? - She stops right at that moment.
So you bring up your mother's greatest interest.
How does a treasure hunt sound?
Bills can be hidden around the house for her.
That's a great idea!
- That's the worst! - Whenever she cleans something,
- she'll find a bill. - Is his mother a mole?
- No. - Is his mother a mole?
That can be done if there's no way to stop her.
Is his mother a mole or what?
(That can be a fun way to be a good son.)
That's enough.
I'll clean that later.
- Will you really clean it? - Yes. I'll do it later.
- I'm going to come and check. - Okay.
Look at how clean it is now.
You should've taken off your socks.
It's okay.
That part is fine.
(Mom's cleaning won't end.)
What are you talking about? This part is the worst.
(What are you talking about? This part is the worst.)
That's enough, Mom.
Pass me the lint roller later.
- Okay. - The white one.
- Let's see. - That's enough.
It's clean now, right?
This should all be brought down to be cleaned,
but I don't want to be going through your things.
Would you like an MBC diary, Mom?
Give me one.
- I got it recently. - I kept talking to her.
- Kang Yong knows what to do. - I constantly got her interest.
Mothers love diaries.
Check this out.
(There's something else I want to show you, Mom.)
"Election 2025."
- These were your lines? - Yes.
You'll be Kang Da Eun. I'll be me.
Look. I'll start.
(The actual script her son used with his partner)
The election race is heading toward the finish line.
I'm here as the final commentator.
I'm Ko Kang Yong.
(His mother starts smiling.)
I'm Kang Da Eun.
It isn't over yet, everyone.
- She has a great voice. - The real race starts now.
No. You have to sound more enthusiastic.
The election race is heading toward the finish line.
I'm here as the final commentator.
I'm Ko Kang Yong.
- I'm Kang Da Eun. - Right.
- It isn't over yet, everyone. - There you go.
- The real race starts now. - Right.
- She's great at that. - Her voice sounds very young.
- Right. - I'm serious.
- Her voice hasn't changed at all. - Right.
It was my dream to become a voice actress.
I wanted to become one.
- She has a great voice. - I love her tone.
(She starts chuckling after forgetting about the cleaning.)
- Gosh. - Cleaning is over now.
We have to head out to eat.
I made a reservation.
Did he make a reservation?
(Approaching)
(Helping her)
(She gets ready to leave with her son's help.)
I'm feeling great.
- I'll get my bag. - Right.
Let's tidy this up.
I'll sort them out. I'll put the T-shirts away.
- I'll put them away. - I want to clear out everything.
I'll do it when you go home. We have to eat.
Take a picture with Wilson.
Oh, right.
- Like this? - Yes.
(Laughing)
Done.
- He changed the subject again. - Kang Yong knows what to do.
He's really good at it.
(They head out to eat after cleaning the house.)
Gosh! They're setting up a tree! It looks amazing.
- Right. - Hyun Moo did his running here.
- Around here. - Was it here?
Oh, right! He went past Gwanghwamun.
What?
Gosh, I laughed so much.
(They head somewhere past Gwanghwamun.)
He said, "I Live Alone is great."
- Dad said that? - Right.
(They sing together her favorite song.)
(Will we be able to love?)
(Singing)
I can't sing out loud right now.
- You just did, Mom. - I did?
I'm someone who can sing "Tears" by So Chan Whee.
Gosh, really?
Is she the master of high notes?
(That is just the love that is felt)
- Gosh! - Gosh!
She sings the high notes really well.
- You can hit them now. - Right.
(They arrive at Hongdae after her passionate singing.)
- Should I get off? - Yes. Get off carefully.
- To the left, Mom. - Right.
(They head into a building.)
- Here it is. - Is it a restaurant? Am I wrong?
- Hello. - Hello.
Can we get your name which you made a reservation with?
Right. I made a reservation under Ko Kang Yong.
- I will lead you to your table. - Right.
Is it a steak restaurant?
I chose this place with care.
(The place Kang Yong made a reservation for)
I chose a fine dining restaurant.
I prepared a course meal for my mother.
Great job.
My mom and dad always go to the same places.
It's always the same sundae gukbap place...
and the same bean sprout gukbap place.
So we went to Jeonju together,
and I treated them to a fine dining meal...
with my MBC bonus.
- Great job. - It's our second fine dining meal.
It's the second fine dining meal for both of us.
It would be great if you could prepare the course meal...
I made a reservation for.
I heard the plating here was done beautifully.
The food is served nicely.
- It's here. - Right.
(He chose this restaurant based on his mother's tastes.)
- Thank you. - Here you are.
Starting from the amuse-bouche,
- we will serve you today's dishes. - Right.
Here are four different finger foods with the cleanser soup.
- Food must look nice, right? - Yes.
It would be great to visit those places with your parents...
- from time to time. - Right.
Those places shouldn't always be visited with your girlfriend.
You have to bring your parents to those places.
Are you saying that to yourself?
(Flustered)
- Well... - Why are you talking to yourself?
Can't you bring me to a place like that?
Just have some sundaeguk with me.
How do we eat this?
Do we use this? Oh, our hands?
Oh, our hands?
- Like this? - In one bite.
(Eating it in one bite)
Gosh, it's delicious.
It's good, isn't it?
That's lovely to see.
(He takes a bite after seeing his mother enjoy it.)
I felt nervous about whether she would say it's good.
- You're a great son. - Gosh.
I think she was satisfied at this moment.
Right? It's fascinating.
It's very refreshing.
(Relieved)
It's here.
Excuse me.
(Looking carefully)
The second course is the salad with vegetables...
and the pita bread with the chimichurri salsa.
I'm curious about how it tastes as it looks nice.
(Crunchy)
It's nice and sour with the beet.
(Grabbing the bread)
Bring up your spoon. I'll get you some.
Just a little. That's enough.
You should have two.
- You should have two. - It's yours.
This is beautiful.
He takes care of his mother well.
How is it?
Spring hasn't come yet.
- It's a feast of spring flowers. - A feast of spring flowers?
- It's lovely. - What a way to put it.
My son did well to choose this place.
- The food must suit her taste. - She's enjoying the food.
Wasn't there something unique about the food?
It's delicious.
There wasn't any seafood or meat.
- Right. - Right.
This is a vegan course meal.
- I see. - It's just made with vegetables.
- That explains. - It's a vegan meal?
You always have the steamed cabbage...
- and vegetables. - Right.
That makes sense.
(His mother is vegan.)
At around October...
in 2022,
she was just about to reach the late stage of colorectal cancer.
She went through anticancer therapy for 3 to 4 months.
Even after that, she had to rest...
for a year or two.
Before all that happened,
I called her once every three months.
I visited her once every six months.
I was a terrible son.
But after she went through that, I called her every single day.
I went back home once a week.
From Busan to Gunsan.
I suddenly felt that I should be seeing her often.
That was when I really tried my best to do that.
After getting diagnosed with colorectal cancer,
- did her diet change? - Yes.
She used to love eating meat.
Every morning,
she eats cabbage or vegetables.
That was why I wanted to treat her to a different vegan meal.
There was a moment when I felt something similar.
My younger brother said this.
"You should visit..."
"at least once a month."
I asked why and he said this.
"Even if you visit Mom and Dad once a month,"
"that's around ten times a year."
"That's about it."
That really spoke to me.
- The numbers made it so clear. - Right.
- Right. - Right.
That made me want to visit my parents more often.
You love eggplants, right?
I love eggplants. I eat them very often.
I eat them often.
Her son got a job...
and is taking her to these places now.
(Feeling proud)
How was last week's news?
You always look great. It's my son, you're talking about.
She watches all of my shows.
I watched your news shows. Also,
you were in the I Live Alone Field Day.
I watched that more than 20 times.
- Gosh. - I barely came out in that.
This is what I talked about with your dad.
We wondered how much you would shine...
while being between famous people.
When you ran while wearing a suit,
you started to shine.
All of my friends called me...
and worried about you with your messy hair...
after running in a suit.
That was why I said, "Didn't that make him shine more?"
And they all agreed.
- Right. - Right.
You were the star of that day, Kang Yong.
- On that day? - The star of the Field Day.
This was the moment that made me clap.
You were an excellent runner.
- You were so fast. - When I went past Woo Il.
Gosh, Kang Yong is really fast.
It's unbelievable that he beat me while wearing a suit.
So you love seeing your son do well.
Right. It's the same for all parents.
All I can see is my son.
I saw who did what to you.
Kian84 dusted the flour on you from behind.
I didn't know that.
That proves that she watched it over and over.
Jae Hyeon dusted the flour off of you from front to back.
- There's a lot on me? - Yes.
Those are brief moments.
(Kang Yong is the star in her eyes in every scene.)
I can see those things naturally.
Gosh, I should've taken care of Kang Yong.
I dusted the flour off of you without a word.
That's something really impressive to do.
(Smirking)
Did Hyun Moo not do anything for me?
When you were running,
he told everyone to look at you.
- He said you were running outward. - That was Dae Ho.
- No. It was Hyun Moo. - Gosh.
He went past him while running outward!
- So it really was me who said that. - How does she remember all that?
I watched it so many times.
So the ones who took care of me stood out to you.
Right.
- I realized that... - That's touching to hear.
There were a lot of great people around you.
(The vegan main dish appears.)
Is this soy meat?
Yes. It's soy meat.
It looks like real meat.
Soy meat?
It's been a while since I've had soy meat.
(She softly cuts a piece...)
(and takes a bite.)
How is it?
This is great.
I'm curious. I've never tried any.
It tasted just like a short rib patty.
(Checking her)
It makes you full even though small portions are served.
Right.
I'm slowly starting to get full.
Of course. This will surely make you full.
I love meals that are like this.
- He must've prepared something. - He's getting ready.
So I kept checking her like that.
It looks so obvious.
- I will use the restroom, Mom. - Okay.
It's quite filling, isn't it?
- Right. - I'm feeling full.
(He heads to the parking lot outside the restaurant.)
Finally!
(Bumping)
It must be a gift.
Gosh!
- He was in a hurry. - It's a gift for her?
My head is too big.
Gosh, it's cold.
I need some background music.
(He carefully returns after getting the things.)
(Peeking)
(Happy birthday to you)
(Confused)
- It's her birthday? - It's her birthday.
- I see. - Her birthday is on December 21.
I knew I wouldn't be able to see her that day,
so I wanted to throw her a surprise in advance...
while she came to visit.
Happy birthday to you
Gosh!
- What a lovely sight. - You should check what's inside.
Open it up.
(Curious)
"Happy birthday."
"Don't hide your joy after receiving the gift..."
"and make sure to show it."
It's my mom's birthday soon.
My small treasure.
Why are you her small treasure?
- Big treasure? - That's my older sister.
- Happy birthday! - Gosh.
- Thank you, my son. - It's for you.
- Gosh, thank you. - Open it up.
What do you think it is?
I wonder.
- What could it be? - What is it?
(Smiling brightly)
What is it?
What is that?
- My goodness! - It's money!
(A cake full of bills)
Did you prepare that in the morning?
I worked on it a bit the night before.
- You just finished it? - I just finished it in the morning.
My goodness!
- How much does this look like? - That's great.
I don't know. Does that really matter right now?
- Look here. - Of course, it matters.
- Right. - It has a golden bill as well.
- Is it 300 dollars? - You think it's 300 dollars?
Right.
It's less than that.
- No? Then it should be 250 dollars. - It's 270 dollars.
Gosh.
You should've filled it to be 300 dollars.
- Why 270 dollars? - I put in a golden bill.
- You should've gone up to 300. - Well,
there were only 23 pockets.
You could've forced in the bills to reach 300 dollars.
Or you should've put in 270 dollars in the cake...
and brought out the 30 dollars as a surprise.
- "Here they are!" - That would've been nice.
That makes it go up to 300.
Why won't you do that yourself with all of those ideas?
- Why? - I'll probably do that someday.
- I should try that. - Bring out the bills as a surprise.
But...
- there's another one. - There's another one.
- I divided it up. - You really wanted these.
I did?
The sneakers?
Shoes? Oh, they're sneakers.
- She likes sneakers? - Really?
- Gosh, they look lovely. - Really?
Check the grip as well.
She always mentioned them when we talked on the phone.
- "Your aunt said they were great." - She wanted them as well.
- She made it obvious. - She made it obvious.
Right. I kept thinking about them.
That was why.
(Laughing)
Slowly.
- The laces should be loosened. - Hold on.
But...
Try jumping.
Gosh, it feels great.
- She looks excited. - Try moving around.
- This brand... - The tone of her voice...
- definitely went up. - Right.
- It went right up. - There's a difference.
- There's certainly a difference. - I think you might not wear them.
It looks nice. Great.
Put on the left one as well.
(Smiling)
Come here, my son.
Thank you. I'll use them well.
I should stay healthy for a long time...
- to make you good food. - Right.
Let's go to Jeju Island at the start of next year.
Sure.
We'll go to Japan at the end of next year.
When was the last time you went to Jeju Island?
Has it been 50 years?
I went on a retreat when I was a junior in high school.
Right. You didn't go ever since that, right?
I've never been to Jeju Island after that.
We should travel together for a long time.
Let's travel together.
I'll be healthy for a long time.
Thank you.
Gosh.
Why cry? Have some water.
I thought I would cry if my mom cried.
I kept trying to distract her.
Great job.
I always think that...
I have to stay healthy.
Healthy people wouldn't do this,
but this is my prayer I give every morning I wake up.
"Thank you once again today."
"Thank you for allowing me to wake up in good health."
I always need to hear my mom's voice.
I want to treat my mom to the best food.
I want to give her the best clothes.
I want to take her to the best places.
I want to get her the best things in this world.
That's who she is to me.
Let's go to Jeju Island and Japan next year.
Let's travel together for a long time.
- Right. I have to stay healthy. - Happy birthday.
- Thank you, my son. - Happy birthday.
I'll stay healthy for a long time...
and not be a burden to you. Okay?
(The Mother and Son's Warm Winter Night)
(Next episode)
(Here's another great son.)
(Mom!)
(Gosh, it's heavy.)
(It's my mother's birthday today.)
(That is why I came out to pick her up.)
(My son's face looks dry.)
(You must not have washed your face.)
(I did wash my face.)
(Looks that make it hard to believe)
(Where have they gone to in the midst of her suspicion?)
(Hello!)
(This is a dog grooming academy...)
(that helps abandoned dogs get adopted.)
(You're lovely.)
(Candy, the pet dog that was with her for 13 years, )
(had to be sent away.)
(His mother struggled a lot because of that.)
(First birthday present: Finding her a new family member)
(Baby!)
(It feels great to see her love it.)
(He resolutely rolls up his sleeves.)
(The oysters and meat get stir-fried.)
(Stir-Fry84 uses his cooking skills.)
(Second birthday present: Homemade birthday meal)
(Humming)
(Slurping)
(The seaweed soup was cooked really well.)
(I'll try a bite as well.)
(It's a bit salty.)
(You're right.)
(Why didn't you tell me?)
It's very salty.
(Just add some water.)
(Good Son84's Day)
(Ju Seung went to the Field Day with strong ambitions.)
(However, he embarrassed himself with terrible stamina.)
(Screaming)
(Shouting)
(To restore his pride, )
(Martial Artist Ju Seung awakens.)
(His training has been upgraded.)
(It's a lot more intense.)
It's fine.
(Look at me.)
(I'm quite impressive.)
(He arrives somewhere after being filled with adrenaline.)
(Minicar shop)
(Martial Artist Ju Seung is equipped with the full energy booster.)
(No one will catch up.)
(I'm Jurad Pitt.)
(I've never lost.)
(The race has begun.)
(Let's go!)
What?
(In the air)
Today...
(Jurad Pitt: The Movie)